A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Political Files, 1958-1972; 10; 15 document box(es)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Livingston County, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 3455)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Madison County, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 3456)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Monroe County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3457)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Montgomery County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3458)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Nassau County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3459)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - New York County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3460)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - New York City, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3461)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Niagara County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3462)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Oneida County, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 3463)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Onondaga County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3464)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Ontario County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3465)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Orange County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3466)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Orleans County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3467)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Oswego County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3468)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Otsego County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3469)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Putnam County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3470)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Queens County, 1970 (Box 114, Folder 3471)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Rensselaer County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3472)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Richmond County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3473)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Rockland County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3474)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - St. Lawrence County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3475)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Saratoga County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3476)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Schenectady County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3477)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Schoharie County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3478)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Schuyler County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3479)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Seneca County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3480)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Steuben County, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 3481)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Suffolk County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3482)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Sullivan County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3483)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Tioga County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3484)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Tomkins County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3485)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Ulster County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3486)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Warren County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3487)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Washington County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3488)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Wayne County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3489)
  - Political Data and Program Data Books - Westchester County, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 3490)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1958-1973; 11; 31 document box(es)
  The files in this subseries were not organized into any of the other subseries. This subseries is not arranged in alphabetical or chronological order but has been left in the original box order created by Diane Van Wie.
  This subseries consists of miscellaneous files, such as newspaper clippings, press releases, notes and drafts, statements, and annual messages.
  - Subject Files - Legislation and Proposals, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 3491)
  - Subject Files - Commerce, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3492)
  - Subject Files - Governor's Conference, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3493)
  - Subject Files - Governor's Notes, undated (Box 117, Folder 3494)
  - Subject Files - Bingo, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3495)
  - Subject Files - Mobilization of Republican Enterprise (MORE) Material, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3496)
  - Subject Files - Urban Development, undated (Box 117, Folder 3497)
  - Subject Files - New York Job Development Authority, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 3498)
  - Subject Files - Mental Hygiene, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 3499)
  - Subject Files - Preservation and Restoration of Historic Sites, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3500)
  - Subject Files - Annual Report of Departmetn of Labor, 1960 (Box 117, Folder 3501)
  - Subject Files - Taxation and Finance, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 3502)
  - Subject Files - Highway Construction Program, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 3503)
  - Subject Files - Public Works, 1959 (Box 117, Folder 3504)
  - Subject Files - Preliminary Report of the Superintendent of Insurance, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 3505)
  - Subject Files - Division for Youth, 1960-1961 (Box 118, Folder 3506)
  - Subject Files - Transportation, 1960-1961 (Box 118, Folder 3507)
  - Subject Files - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 3508)
  - Subject Files - Discrimination, 1958-1961 (Box 118, Folder 3509)
  - Subject Files - Education, 1960-1961 (Box 118, Folder 3510)
  - Subject Files - Employment, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 3511)
    Graph 1957-1961.
  - Subject Files - Puerto Ricans in New York City, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 3512)
  - Subject Files - Master Plan of State University of New York, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 3513)
  - Subject Files - Regional Plan Association Report, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 3514)
  - Subject Files - Mayor Wagner, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 3515)
  - Subject Files - Off Track Betting, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 3516)
  - Subject Files - "Cash, Investment, and Debt Management" (Box 118, Folder 3517)
  - Subject Files - NAR Administration Accomplishments (Box 118, Folder 3518)
  - Subject Files - Hospital Care in Syracuse, 1959-1961 (Box 119, Folder 3519)
  - Subject Files - Opinions on Atlantic Community, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 3520)
  - Subject Files - Opinions on Atlantic Community, undated (Box 119, Folder 3521)
  - Subject Files - The Wagner Years a Profile in Indecision, undated (Box 119, Folder 3522)
  - Subject Files - Alcoholic Beverage - Age, undated (Box 119, Folder 3523)
  - Subject Files - 1960 Budget TV Program, undated (Box 119, Folder 3524)
  - Subject Files - The House of Politics - Digest (Box 119, Folder 3525)
  - Subject Files - Workman's Compensation Law, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 3526)
  - Subject Files - Public Relations Opportunities, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 3527)
  - Subject Files - Juvenile Delinquency, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 3528)
  - Subject Files - Your Future in New York, undated (Box 119, Folder 3529)
  - Subject Files - Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion in the Relation to the Democratic Way of Life, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 3530)
  - Subject Files - Wagner, Walter, 1959 (Box 119, Folder 3531)
  - Subject Files - Frauds of the Tammany Democrats, 1871 (Box 119, Folder 3532)
  - Subject Files - Unemployment, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 3533)
  - Subject Files - Television Program - Higher Education, undated (Box 119, Folder 3534)
  - Subject Files - Legislation Alcohol Level, undated (Box 119, Folder 3535)
  - Subject Files - Television Program Reorganization, undated (Box 119, Folder 3536)
  - Subject Files - Department of State, undated (Box 119, Folder 3537)
  - Subject Files - Mental Hygiene, 1959-1960 (Box 119, Folder 3538)
  - Subject Files - Television Program Jobs, 1960-1961 (Box 119, Folder 3539)
  - Subject Files - 1960 Chamber of Commerce Speech (Box 119, Folder 3540)
  - Subject Files - Housing, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 3541)
  - Subject Files - Education, 1960 (Box 119, Folder 3542)
  - Subject Files - Mount McGregor, undated (Box 119, Folder 3543)
  - Subject Files - Budget Material, 1962-1963 (Box 120, Folder 3544)
  - Subject Files - Budget Message, 1962-1963, 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 3545)
  - Subject Files - Budget Message, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 3546)
  - Subject Files - Message to Defense Council, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3547)
  - Subject Files - Letter to the Governor from George Balanchine, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3548)
  - Subject Files - Summary of Temporary State Commission on Economic Expansion (Box 120, Folder 3549)
  - Subject Files - Digest of Address by James E. Allen, Jr., State Commissioner of Education before the Annual City College of New York, November 14, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3550)
  - Subject Files - Committee on School Financing, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3551)
  - Subject Files - Formula of Foundation Program of State Education Aid, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3552)
  - Subject Files - Relative Local School Tax Burdens, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3553)
  - Subject Files - Review of "Schools of Tomorrow - Today", 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3554)
  - Subject Files - Summary of Address by James Allen at Annual Meeting New York State Council of School Superintendents, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3555)
  - Subject Files - Summary of Commissioner Allen's Analysis of State Aid Program, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3556)
  - Subject Files - Plan for Federated School Districts, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3557)
  - Subject Files - Statement L. Judson Morhouse on School Financing Crisis, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3558)
  - Subject Files - "Teaching Reading Through Closed Circuit Television in the Elementary School", University of the State of New York Report, November 1959 (Box 120, Folder 3559)
  - Subject Files - Analyzing the Compensation of New York State Employees, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3560)
  - Subject Files - Legislative Items for New York State, 1960 (Box 120, Folder 3561)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message to the New York Legislature, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 3562)
  - Subject Files - Department of Commerce Reports of Daniel F. Ruge, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3563)
  - Subject Files - Department of Education, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3564)
  - Subject Files - Department of Labor, 1958-1959 (Box 121, Folder 3565)
  - Subject Files - Division of Budget, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3566)
  - Subject Files - Department of Mental Hygiene, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3567)
  - Subject Files - State Police, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 3568)
  - Subject Files - State University, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3569)
  - Subject Files - Transportation - Railroad Problems, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3570)
  - Subject Files - Mailing Lists of Members and Heads of Organizations and Departmetns (Box 121, Folder 3571)
  - Subject Files - Health Insurance Study, 1959-1960 (Box 121, Folder 3572)
  - Subject Files - Citizens Committee on Traffic Safety, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3573)
  - Subject Files - Civil Defense Confidential Governors' Conference, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3574)
  - Subject Files - Task Force on Fallout Protection, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3575)
  - Subject Files - Civil Defense, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 3576)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message Extra Copies, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 3577)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 3578)
    Governor's copy.
  - Subject Files - Reorganization Materials, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 3579)
  - Subject Files - Special Messages, Joint Statement on New York State, New York City Fiscal Relations, undated (Box 122, Folder 3580)
  - Subject Files - Special Messages Health and Mental Health, 1960 (Box 122, Folder 3581)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3582)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 3583)
  - Subject Files - Inaugural Address, 1959 (Box 122, Folder 3584)
  - Subject Files - Education Legislation, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3585)
  - Subject Files - Griffis Air Force Base, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3586)
  - Subject Files - Heald Report, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3587)
  - Subject Files - Middle Income Housing, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3588)
  - Subject Files - New York State Employees Retirement System, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3589)
  - Subject Files - Railroad Legislation, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3590)
  - Subject Files - Rent Control Legislation, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3591)
  - Subject Files - Salary Information, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3592)
  - Subject Files - Social Welfare, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3593)
  - Subject Files - Analysis Requests Made by Mayor Wagner, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 3594)
  - Subject Files - Budget Dr. T. Norman Hurd, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 3595)
  - Subject Files - Budget Items, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 3596)
  - Subject Files - Civil Defense Legislation, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 3597)
  - Subject Files - Television - What New York State is Doing for You, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 3598)
  - Subject Files - Michael Rockefeller - Form Letters of Appreciation for Condolences from Governor's Cabinet, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 3599)
  - Subject Files - Civil Defense - General Advisory Committee, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3600)
  - Subject Files - Commission on Discrimination in Housing, 1958-1959 (Box 123, Folder 3601)
  - Subject Files - Commission on Economic Expansion, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3602)
  - Subject Files - Commission on Governmental Operation of City of New York, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3603)
  - Subject Files - New York State Commission on Historical Observances, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3604)
  - Subject Files - Commission on Investigation, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3605)
  - Subject Files - Commission on Rents, 1958 (Box 123, Folder 3606)
  - Subject Files - Committee on Law Enforcement, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3607)
  - Subject Files - Committee to Study Power Needs and Resources, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3608)
  - Subject Files - Harness Racing Commission, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3609)
  - Subject Files - Civil Service Employees Association, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3610)
  - Subject Files - Department of Banking, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 3611)
  - Subject Files - Department of Commerce, 1959-1960 (Box 123, Folder 3612)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 3613)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message Drafts, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 3614)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message Drafts, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 3615)
  - Subject Files - Judges in New York State, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3616)
  - Subject Files - New York State Legislature, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3617)
  - Subject Files - Officials of Unions, undated (Box 124, Folder 3618)
  - Subject Files - United States Senators and Representatives, undated (Box 124, Folder 3619)
  - Subject Files - Executive Chamber Staff, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3620)
  - Subject Files - Members of the Press, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3621)
  - Subject Files - Executive Mansion Staff, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3622)
  - Subject Files - New York Congressional Delegation, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3623)
  - Subject Files - Heads of Educational Institutes, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3624)
  - Subject Files - Heads of Organizations, Commercial Enterprises and Banks, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3625)
  - Subject Files - Miscellaneous - Personal, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3626)
  - Subject Files - State Troopers in Executive Chamber, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3627)
  - Subject Files - Federal Government Officials, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3628)
  - Subject Files - Republicans in Other States, undated (Box 124, Folder 3629)
  - Subject Files - Governors United States, undated (Box 124, Folder 3630)
  - Subject Files - New York Republican Organization, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 3631)
  - Subject Files - New York State Executive Officials, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 3632)
  - Subject Files - Scholar Incentive Program, 1961 (Box 124, Folder 3633)
  - Subject Files - Mrs. Murphy Summary Action Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 125, Folder 3634)
  - Subject Files - Legislative Leaders Meeting, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3635)
  - Subject Files - Transportation Commuter Problems, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3636)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3637)
  - Subject Files - Copies of Annual Message, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3638)
  - Subject Files - Budget Speech New York State 1959-1960 Budget Outlook (Box 125, Folder 3639)
  - Subject Files - Budget Message, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3640)
  - Subject Files - Juvenile Delinquency Correspondence, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3641)
  - Subject Files - Emergency Meeting on Juvenile Delinquency, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3642)
  - Subject Files - Little Hoover Commission, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3643)
  - Subject Files - New York City Taxes, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3644)
  - Subject Files - Office of Local Government, 1958-1959 (Box 125, Folder 3645)
  - Subject Files - Task Force on Middle Income Housing, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3646)
  - Subject Files - Water Front Commission, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3647)
  - Subject Files - Transportation - Federal Highway Program and Thruway Reimbursement, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 3648)
  - Subject Files - Transportation - General, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 3649)
  - Subject Files - Transportation - Narrows Bridge, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 3650)
  - Subject Files - Transportation - Port of New York Authority, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 3651)
  - Subject Files - Annual Message to the Legislature, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 3652)
  - Subject Files - Westchester Parks, 1959-1960 (Box 126, Folder 3653)
  - Subject Files - Councils, Commissions, Etc. Information on Telephone Tax, 1960 (Box 126, Folder 3654)
  - Subject Files - Water Resources Agencies, undated (Box 126, Folder 3655)
  - Subject Files - Urban Action Center, 1967-1968 (Box 126, Folder 3656)
  - Subject Files - Urban Action Center, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 3657)
  - Subject Files - Report to the Joint Legislative Committee on Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 126, Folder 3658)
  - Subject Files - Legislative Apportionment, undated (Box 126, Folder 3659)
  - Subject Files - Legislative Apportionment Supplemental Memoranda and Plans, undated (Box 126, Folder 3660)
  - Subject Files - Appointments, Lists and Miscellaneous, 1959-1965 (Box 127, Folder 3661)
  - Subject Files - Governor's Message to the Legislature, January 1959-January 1963 (Box 127, Folder 3662)
  - Subject Files - Appointments, Lists and Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 127, Folder 3663)
  - Subject Files - Department of State Annual Report, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3664)
  - Subject Files - New York State Council on the Arts Annual Report, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3665)
  - Subject Files - New York Report, undated (Box 127, Folder 3666)
  - Subject Files - Proposed Reorganization of the Executive Branch of New York State Government, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 3667)
  - Subject Files - "Futures" State University of New York, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3668)
  - Subject Files - New York State Capitol Fallout Shelter, undated (Box 127, Folder 3669)
  - Subject Files - Interstate - Federal Compact for the Delaware River Basin, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 3670)
  - Subject Files - Staff Information, 1958-1959 (Box 127, Folder 3671)
  - Subject Files - Meeting at White House Briefing Material, February 29, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 3672)
  - Subject Files - Briefing Material for Friday Television Taping, September 1967 (Box 127, Folder 3673)
  - Subject Files - President's Advisory Committee on Government Organization, 1953 (Box 128, Folder 3674)
  - Subject Files - Meeting with Mayor Lindsay and Staff, February 27, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 3675)
  - Subject Files - Organization of Federal Executive Departments and Agencies, 1959 (Box 128, Folder 3676)
  - Subject Files - Appointments Dairy, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 3677)
  - Subject Files - Republican National Convention 1964 - Tally Sheets (Box 128, Folder 3678)
  - Subject Files - Fact Sheets on Research Questions, July 1962 (Box 128, Folder 3679)
  - Subject Files - Potential Sites for the Urban Development Corporation, 1967 (Box 128, Folder 3680)
  - Subject Files - Program Proposals, December 16, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 3681)
  - Subject Files - Summer Camping Program Meeting, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 3682)
  - Subject Files - Federal Tax Reform, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 3683)
  - Subject Files - New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority - Background for Meeting with Secretary David Kennedy, 1970 (Box 129, Folder 3684)
  - Subject Files - A System for Defining Goals for New York State, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 3685)
    Office of Planning Coordination.
  - Subject Files - Social Development, undated (Box 129, Folder 3686)
  - Subject Files - Education Programs, undated (Box 129, Folder 3687)
  - Subject Files - Housing Programs, undated (Box 129, Folder 3688)
  - Subject Files - Natural Resources, undated (Box 129, Folder 3689)
  - Subject Files - Health Programs, undated (Box 129, Folder 3690)
  - Subject Files - Transportation, undated (Box 129, Folder 3691)
  - Subject Files - Recreation and Culture, undated (Box 129, Folder 3692)
  - Subject Files - General Government Programs, undated (Box 129, Folder 3693)
  - Subject Files - Economic Development, undated (Box 129, Folder 3694)
  - Subject Files - National Governors' Conference, December 16-17, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 3695)
  - Subject Files - National Governors' Conference, December 16-17, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 3696)
  - Subject Files - Meeting of Republican Governor's Association, December 9-10, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 3697)
  - Subject Files - Meeting of Republican Governor's Association, December 9-10, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 3698)
  - Material for GOP Governor's Association Meeting, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 3699)
  - National Governors' Conference Interim Meeting, December 16-17, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 3700)
  - Governors' Conference on Manpower Training, June 2, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 3701)
  - Mrs. Ann Whitman Copy National Governors' Conference, October 16-24, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 3702)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Problems of Public Health and Medicare, May 24, 1966 (Box 130, Folder 3703)
  - Chronological Record of South Mall Negotiations, 1963-1964 (Box 130, Folder 3704)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, May 12, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 3705)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, July 15, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 3706)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, September 15, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 3707)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, November 14, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 3708)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, November 14, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 3709)
  - Coordinating Committee on the South Mall Project - Progress Report, January 15, 1970 (Box 130, Folder 3710)
  - A Survey of the Political Climate in Nassau County, New York, February 1970 (Box 130, Folder 3711)
  - Public Opinion of New York State's Problems, December 1964 (Box 130, Folder 3712)
  - Index to Issue Books, 1958-1962 (Box 131, Folder 3713)
  - Aging Book Volume I, 1958-1962 (Box 131, Folder 3714)
  - Action for Our Cities, A Preliminary Report, Part I - Public Order and Control of Crime, 1967 (Box 131, Folder 3715)
  - "A Total Community for Floyd Bennett Field", December 1970 (Box 131, Folder 3716)
  - The Catholic School System of the Archdiocese of New York - A Financial Study, March 1969 (Box 131, Folder 3717)
  - Economic Development and Consumer Protection, undated (Box 132, Folder 3718)
  - A Proposal for a Comprehensive Manpower Agency, March 1, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 3719)
  - Federal Legislation: Higher Education, Drugs, Child Development, Manpower, 1971-1972 (Box 132, Folder 3720)
  - Summary of Wallace Survey Data, September 1978 (Box 132, Folder 3721)
  - Planning for the Development in New York State Office of Planning Coordination, January 1969 (Box 132, Folder 3722)
  - Delaware River Basin Commission Meeting, March 7, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 3723)
  - Report of the Committee on Human Resources, 1972 (Box 132, Folder 3724)
  - Governor's Conference Commemorating the 100th Anniversary of the New York State Board of Social Welfare, November 2-3, 1967 (Box 132, Folder 3725)
  - Material from the Governor's Conference, January 23, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 3726)